Contact

03242527832 (Home) engr.rehan786@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/m-rehan-077a8683 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C#
Microsoft SQL Server
OOP

M. Rehan

Senior Software Engineer | .NET Core | Node | React | Redis | Mongodb | SQL | MYSQL | Identity Server | Micro-services | CI/CD | Twilio APIs | HubSpot APIs

Pakistan

Summary

i am a major in computer engineering with BS degree in computer engineering and love programming on different platform specially on Microsoft.i love web and mobile apps development. Having two years hands-on experience in Software development projects including both team-based projects and self-managed projects.

Experience

TRG - The Resource Group 2 years 7 months

Senior Software Engineer July 2021 - Present (4 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Software Engineer April 2019 - July 2021 (2 years 4 months)

Digital Dividend Senior Software Engineer June 2018 - April 2019 (11 months) Karachi

TRAFIX LLC

1 year 10 months

Senior Software Engineer September 2017 - June 2018 (10 months) karachi

Software Engineer September 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 1 month) Karachi Logic-Unit Software Developer Internship June 2014 - May 2015 (1 year)

Worked on User Management, sales and purchase modules of an ERP with C#, ADO.Net and SQL server 2012.

Education

Sir Syed University of Engineering and Technology Bachelor's Degree, Computer Engineering · (2012 - 2015)

Sindh Muslim Science Collage Intermediate, Pre-Engineering · (2010 - 2011)